nareponline.com 2016-03-22

# Privacy Policy

_  
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which[ Pearl Street Enterprises LLC](http://pearl.st/ "Pearl Street Privacy Policy") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the refdesk.org website(s) and app(s) ("Sites"). This privacy policy applies to the Sites and all products and services offered by Pearl Street Enterprises LLC._Disclaimer: 

All content provided or linked via our apps is DMCA compliant and licensed under Creative Commons or in the Public Domain. Please notify us immediately if you have any questions regarding this issue.

Personal identification information:

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Sites, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Sites. Users may visit our Sites anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information:

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Sites. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Sites, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. Web browser cookies Our Sites may use "cookies" to enhance User experience.

User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Sites may not function properly. How we use collected information Pearl Street Enterprises LLC may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: - To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. - To improve our Sites We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. - To send periodic emails If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

We do not currently maintain a list of user details for the purpose of email communication. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Sites.

How we protect your information:

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Sites. Sharing your personal information We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. Third party websites Users may find advertising or other content on our Sites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties.

We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Sites, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Advertising:

Ads appearing on our Sites may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Google Adsense Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Sites and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Etc:

Changes to this privacy policy Pearl Street Enterprises LLC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. Your acceptance of these terms.

By using our Sites, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at the information below.

Corporate Contact:
